dtscout.com 2018-12-29

# Technology Privacy Policy

This privacy policy addresses DTS Technology Privacy Policy and it is not to be confused with this websites’ privacy policy.

Any reference to “us”, “we”, ”DTS” or “ours relates to DTScout, reference to “user/s”, “you” or “your” relate to individuals that use or where exposed to DTS Technology. “Partners” or “Data Partners” relate to third party data companies and advertisers (demand Partners) and publisher websites/online services that distribute DTS Technology (supply Partners). The following privacy statement explains how users’ information is collected and shared with our Partners and reviews how we protect users privacy.

By using our Technology, visiting this website or visiting our supply Partners’ websites you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this DTS Technology Privacy Policy. Additionally you consent to adhering to privacy guidelines that are at least as strict as the guidelines set forth.

WE WILL NOT USE OR SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH ANYONE EXCEPT AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

Collection:

DTS does not actively collect nor store any personally identifiable information (PII) such as names, email or residence addresses, telephone numbers, etc. Other than PII you explicitly provide voluntarily on our website contact form or via direct communication.

Use:

Personal Information shall be used solely in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. Furthermore, DTS obligates its Partners to do the same. This means that neither our Partners nor us can relate any of the information we collect or aggregate to an individual user.

While personal information or PII could be used for identifying a specific person and relay information to that person; non personal information (NPII) on its own cannot be associated with a specific person but may assist in personalizing content and hold commercial value (interested in cars and education, speaks English, using a mobile device, etc.). Based on NPII a user may be anonymously associated with audiences and receive more personalized content and advertisement.

Only information of commercial value is collected and retained for limited periods (see below), and generally relates to:

  1. Demographics: Approximated geographic location (country/city), spoken language.
  2. Behavioral: Advertising interaction, sites visited and searches conducted in the DTS network.
  3. Technical: Screen resolution, browser attributes, IP address (assigned automatically to any user when connecting to the Internet).

Collection:

We use various technologies (see below) in order to automatically collect NPII on our supply partners’ websites and through their services. We collect the NPII directly or indirectly through our demand partners. All DTS demand Partners are leading companies that took upon themselves to comply with self-regulatory privacy protection criteria.

Use:

In order to allow for more efficient and relevant ad serving, DTS and its Partners may collect, share and aggregate NPII (with third party NPII). This generally results in segmenting and categorizing the data in order to create interest-based audiences (traveling, autos, entertainment, etc.). The goal is to facilitate more efficient and relevant online advertising, in this case, using anonymous data.

Disclaimer:

Please note the following reservations with regard to our Partners, for which we have no affiliation with or responsibility for any of their activities:

  * We recommend you review Partners’ respective privacy policies, links available in our “data Partners” section. Partners’ activity is subject to their respective policies and practices.
  * You may be required to visit Partners’ websites in order to opt out their cookies. Relevant links may be present in our “data Partners” section.
  * While we require our partners to uphold this privacy policy, we do not monitor or control such third parties cookies and accordingly we are not responsible or liable in any manner to the type of information collected by such third parties cookies. If you would like to file a compliant regarding such third party activity you can contact us at [privacy@dtscout.com](mailto:privacy@dtscout.com?subject=DTScout%20Privacy%20Inquiry).
  * We are not responsible for any of the content published on supply Partners’ websites.
  * We may offer in our documentation and/or website Partners’ summaries, logos and links to their websites and third party publications and/or websites may refer or link to our website; this should not be seen as notice of affiliation, endorsement, authorization or representation.

We use cookies and other technologies in order to collect non-PII (NPII), identify and track anonymously and continuously users’ online behavior in order to improve industry’s ability to offer them personalized content.

A cookie is a small text file that is stored in a web browser directory by a website or an advertisement related action. There are two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are created temporarily in your web browser directory while you are visiting a website and deleted once you leave the website. The persistent cookies remain in your web browser and are activated again once you visit the website that created that such specific cookie. A web beacon is a small file used by a website or a service to keep track of your navigation through a single website or a series of websites A pixel is a small line of code which is used by a website or an advertisement related action to assign online activities to a computer or browser.

DTS respects your choices with regard to online privacy, you can opt-out at any time using the following opt out link in order to opt-out from DTS services. Please note that your browser enables you to disable all cookies (if you do not know how to do this, consult with your browsers’ "Help" tab), however, this may interfere with your use of various online services and websites.

Opting out results in embedding opt-out cookies on your browser that notify demand side servers not to interact with your browser: if you delete/purge cookies and remove the said opt out cookie, upgrade or use a different computer or browser, or take any action which results in the deletion of the "opt out" cookie than you will need to opt out again.

You may wish to wish the following opt out tools to manage your choices from various advertising networks:  

You can utilize our data retrieval tool to request a copy of your data or request your data be delete from our systems. Inquries will be responded to as soon as possible via the email address provided in the form. To utilize this servive please click on the "User Requests" section of the Privacy Center. 

DTS does not collect or store sensitive information such as personally identifiable information other than IP addresses. No data related to political, ethnic or racial origins, philosophical, sexual or religious orientation, health condition, financial condition, children under the age of 13 and other sensitive categories as per [OBA](http://www.iabeurope.eu/) guidelines.

DTS’s servers are located in the United States (US) and Canada (CA); you should know that your information is transferred to the US and/or Canada while you may be exposed to our Technology from anywhere in the world. Be advised that US and Canadian laws governing the collection, disclosure and use of your information (PII and NPII) may differ from the information legislation present in your territory. Through your continued use of the Technology you agree to accept US and/or Canadian information related law.

Note that although we take measures to secure the information and reduce the risk of unwanted disclosure, we cannot guarantee the information will not be exposed as a result of unauthorized penetration to our servers.

It is supply Partners’ and their respective supply Partners’ responsibility to take any action required to uphold regulatory requirements and inform their users adequately that their websites use third party technology and cookies that assist in collection and sharing of anonymous NPII of commercial relevance to online behavioral advertising.

Supply Partners are obligated to present a clear, prominent and permanent notification or link to such notification in all pages where DTS Technology is being used. Said notice should offer an opt-out link and can link to the DTS Technology Privacy Policy in order to improve transparency and empower users’ choices. Proper notice and an opt-out link should also be offered in the relevant website’s privacy policies.

We may share some or all of your information (PII and NPII) with our subsidiaries, joint ventures or other companies under a common control that we have or may have in the future, or such third parties that acquire us or substantially all of our assets, providing such party undertakes to protect your privacy in accordance with these terms.

Otherwise, we will not disclose your Personal Information to any third party, unless:

  * Required to do so as part of any legal proceedings conducted between you and the Website.
  * Required to do so by court order.
  * In case the activity of the Website/Technology is transferred to a third party, providing such party undertakes to protect your privacy in accordance with these terms.

Please contact us at [privacy@dtscout.com](mailto:privacy@dtscout.com?subject=DTScout%20Privacy%20Inquiry) if you have further questions, concerns or complaints having to do with DTS privacy related practices.

This policy was last updated on May 20, 2018.
